# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Displacement",
    answer: "Change in position of an object",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Average Speed",
    answer: "Total distance divided by the total time travelled",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Instantaneous speed",
    answer: "The speed of an object at a particular instant in time",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Velocity",
    answer: "The rate of change of position of a body in a specific direction",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Acceleration",
    answer: "The rate of the velocity of an object with respect to time",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Center of Gravity",
    answer: "The point from which the weight of a body or system is acting. Also known as Center of Mass",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Torque",
    answer: "The measure of the force that can cause an object to rotate about an axis",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Workdone",
    answer: "The measure of energy transferred by a force acting through a distance",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Energy",
    answer: "The ability to do work",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Power",
    answer: "The rate at which work is done",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Power",
    answer: "The rate at which work is done",
    course_name: "Basic Definitions",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Specific Heat Capacity",
    answer: "This is the heat required to raise the temperature of the unit mass of a given amount of substance. Also known as Enthalpy",
    course_name: "Specific Heat Capacity",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Specific Heat Capacity is measured at...",
    answer: "constant pressure or isobaric",
    course_name: "Specific Heat Capacity",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Thermal Heat of Expansion",
    answer: "The tendency of matter to change its shape, area, and volume as a result of change in temperature",
    course_name: "Specific Heat Capacity",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})

Flashcard.create({
    question: "Law of Conservation of Energy",
    answer: "States that the total energy of an isolated system remains constant. Energy can can neither be created nor destroyed",
    course_name: "Specific Heat Capacity",
    course_subject: "Physics"
})
